CURRICULUM VITAE Lindah Kelida Wamalwa

PERSONAL INFORMATION	
_	Lindah Kelida Wamalwa (+254)701922528   Ikelida@gmail.com
OBJECTIVES	
	To find a stable job security which will be an opportunity to educate myself and network more on a professional level. In this way, I will enhance my professional skills in order to advance and be an expert in my field of expertise.
SKILLS	After sale, Big data and data analytics Computer, laptop maintenance and repair, Confidence, Dealing with difficult people, Direct sales, Domain name systems (DNS), E-mail and internet Emotional control, Leadership Marketing, Network regulation, Office tools: Word, Excel, Outlook, Problem solving, Public speaking, Reporting, Retail banking, SWIFT Sales strategy, Team building, Teamwork UNIX Virtualization.
EDUCATION BACKGROUND	
Sept 2014 – Dec 2018	Bachelor of Science in Mathematics The University of Nairobi Majored in Operations Research with units in Programming Methodology, Mathematical Modelling, Linear programming, Design and Analysis of Algorithms and Stochastic Processes).
Jan 2010 – Nov 2013	Kenya Certificate of Secondary Examinations The Sacred Heart Mukumu Girls High School. Mean Grade: A- (minus).
WORK EXPERIENCE	
July 2019 – June 2020	ICT Authority ICT intern under the Presidential Digital Talent Program working with Kenya Revenue Authority with responsibilities in: - Overseeing installation of new anti-virus software and critical system update - Test and evaluate all new technology e.g. database systems, websites.
<b>April 2019 – July 2019</b>	National Bank of Kenya

CURRICULUM VITAE Lindah Kelida Wamalwa

Direct Sales Representative.

- Managed selling of various products in a professional manner.
- Developed new business prospects in specific geographic areas through cold calls.
- Interacted with existing customers to increase sales of the bank's products and services.

# TRAININGS AND OTHER COURSES

Honors and awards

# **Internet Society Certificate - 2019**

In Introduction to Networks Operations: UNIX/Linux, Networking and DNS.

# Google Digital Skills for Africa - 2019

Having acquired a certificate in The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing.

#### **Huawei Certification- 2019**

Recognized as HCIA Routing and switching.

### The Ascent- 2018

## Training program in leadership

Certificate in leadership – University of Nairobi.

# Mathematics Association for Nairobi University -2016

# Certificate in Computer and Statistical Packages in

Advanced Excel, C++ and MATLAB Computational Software.

#### **Interests and Hobbies**

Dancing, singing, listening to music and intense reading.

### REFEREES

### Josephat Yator:

ICT Manager, Western Region, Kenya Revenue Authority, Tel; +254721861671, Josephat, Yator@kra.go.ke.

# John Tarus:

Branch Manager, South C Kebs, National Bank of Kenya, Tel; +254722235475, jtarus@nationalbank.co.ke.

#### Jack Shihundu:

Human Resource Manager, White Rose Dry Cleaners, Tel; +254721671722, jackshihundu@whiterose.co.ke.